

# NIKITA CARIKJ

#### **ABOUT ME**

Customer support rep with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software and sales industry. Responsible for observing current policies and procedures and analyzing their effectiveness. Developing solutions to company issues and finding effective ways to provide a positive experience for customers.

### SKILLS

Data entry
Data analysis
Excel
JIRA
QA Testing
Writing

## **CONTACT**

+389 71 349 741 ncarikj@gmail.com

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **PANCE KARAGOZOV**

2014 - 2018 | Lab Technician

# FACULTY OF NATURAL SCIENCES AND MATHEMATICS

2019- | Nutritionism

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2019- ANHOCH 2020 Sales Specialist

- Maximize the sales performance
- Establishing strong relationships and gaining insight to the needs and lifestyle of the client
- Perform incisive and insightful market and competitive research

2019- FREELANCE 2021 Content Writer

- Determine the clearest and most logical way to present information for greatest reader comprehension
- Analyze information required for the development
- Delivering projects quickly and meeting deadlines

2020-Present

#### **PABAU CLINIC SOFTWARE**

Customer Support Representative

- Receiving and placing customer service telephone calls
- Maintaining solid customer relationships
- Resolving customer complaints, managing database records, drafting status reports on customer service issues